Juan Carlos Saugar

juancarlossa.github.io

(2) +34622695144

github.com/juancarlossa



Profile

Spaniard willing to start developing in Poland. Student of *Computer Science* (*Informatyka*) in Uniwersytet Opolski. Self-learner of **Frontend**, **Back-end** and **Linux**. Using **JavaScript**, ReactJS and NodeJS. Nowadays learning ethical hacking - Pentesting, Docker and Linux. Languages teacher for more than 3 years

Work experience

Semper Avanti Opole - Volunteering

09/2019 - 09/2020 • Opole, Poland

- Designed posters and fliers to promote our events, using Canva
- Created language events for young people in Opole

Szkoła Języków Obcych Master

03/2020 - Nowadays **Q** Opole, Poland

 Teaching Spanish language to young people and adults: individual and groups

Projects

React portfolio github.com/juancarlossa/juancarlossa.github.io.git

- Static website built with React, Gatsby and Emotion
- Created components using Styled-components
- Personal portfolio created in order to host the main projects I will be creating.

HTML project github.com/juancarlossa/portfolio-HTML.git

- Simple project created with HTML and CSS
- Using CSS technologies: Bootstrap and SaSS.
- The main goal of this portfolio is to add more functionalities and improve the performance of the previous project.

Arch Linux OS

- Installed Arch on a Virtual machine, using Bash scripting
- Personally I installed it to learn about Linux and practice Pentesting on <u>HackTheBox.com</u>

Skills

Programming languages

- JavaScript (ES6)
- TypeScript
- HTML, CSS
- PHP
- C#
- SQL

Operating Systems

- Windows
- Linux (Arch)

Technologies

- React
- SQL
- Bash Node.js
- Git
- Wordpress

Design

Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightrooms, Adobe XD

Languages

English Spanish Olish Russian Olish

German •••

Education

Uniwersytet Opolski

2021 - Currently // Opole, Poland Computer Science Engineering -Faculty of IT

Uniwersytet Opolski

2020 - Currently // Opole, PolandBachelor of **Comercial Language** Faculty of Filology

Now learning

Cibersecurity, Docker, Linux

Interests

Gym, languages, guitar, cooking